This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy is rushing to Navy Headquarters to rescue his brother Ace from public execution.
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard Pirates have successfully stormed Marine Ford to save Ace
and triggered an all-out war with the Navy.
Oars!
Don't worry Ace, I can make it for sure!
Oars, all-out war!
Oars!
Doble Man!
Spocky Shadow Lizard!
Justice for the Winners!
Sengoku Strategy in Action!
The winners! Sengoku Strategy in Action!
Shishi! See? Now that's how you do it. That is some good murder.
No! Captain Ors!
Damn you! You warlord scumbag!
Captain!
Ors, no!
I'm here.
Please stop.
I'm sorry.
I'm here is my friend.
Frank.
Jessica!
I'm sorry.
Ours!
I'll have to fix up that foot of his, but that's a small price to pay for another giant zombie!
This is so cool!
Oh, oars...
Shouldn't drop your guard, Whitebeard!
Dicepulons!
Okay...
Uh...
Everybody just leave Whitebeard alone, I guess...
Dicepulons!
My son.
Dodge!
This is beautiful.
Doflamingo!
You're gonna pay for what you did to Ores,
and I'm gonna collect a debt.
What the hell are you laughing at?
How are you not laughing?
We're standing on the fulcrum of history itself.
The future and past will be written here.
Quit your hammering and die!
Take him down, boss!
Stop dancing around and fight for real!
Pizza!
You're Admiral Yukimura!
I can't do this.
I'm scared and I'm weak and I'm useless.
Even our leaders are falling one after another.
There's no way a loser like me is going to survive out there.
Wait, Kobi. I'm running away too.
Get back to the battlefield.
Just let me go.
Please, sir.
What's Admiral Aka-Inu doing here?
I can't die like this.
I'm terrified to leave my family on their own.
Please, I'm begging you, Admiral.
Please!
As soldiers of the Navy,
we carry the weight of the justice of the world on our backs
and will gladly die to defend it.
Any man who turns tail and runs
doesn't deserve to call himself a Marine,
let alone a man for that matter.
the most he could be called is
a waste of life.
If you truly care about your family as you say,
you'll only shame them by living.
No, he killed one of his own soldiers?
Admiral Tsukasugi, we're ready to proceed with the operation.
Excellent. It's finally time.
The operation?
Ace!
Go! Everyone get through the space ores bay!
The bay is ours!
Right, let's destroy the bay head! Go open up another entrance!
Aim straight ahead and fire!
Dammit! Hardly a scratch!
Leave it to me!
A nice cutter?
It's the Ice Witch, Whitey Bay!
I've cut plenty of glaciers tougher than that!
Alright, let's move! The path is open!
Right behind you! All clear!
It's time to move into the bay!
Yeah!
Is something the matter, Water Buffalo Atmos?
You seem like you've gone a little stiff.
What? What did you do?
My body! I can't control it!
Commander Atmos!
Stay back! Don't get anywhere near me!
What's wrong, Commander?
Now!
Let us fight, boss!
Stay away!
I don't understand, Commander! Why?
He's got control of my body!
Tell Flamingo, you bastard!
Stop it!
Please, no!
Pirates are evil. The Navy is just.
But that's only true because history tells us so.
Children who've never known peace have different values
than children who've never known war.
The one who wins will rewrite the definition of right and wrong.
They'll decide the future and how the past is written.
Will justice prevail?
Why, there's no other way!
The winner will define the meaning of justice!
They've broken through the bay head at two different points, sir!
There's nothing left to prevent Whitebeard's allies from entirely flooding the area!
I'm afraid we've got no way to hold them back, sir!
What should we do now?
Don't worry about it.
We're ready.
Put the plan into action.
It's about time.
Out of the way!
Either stand down or die!
Move it, you old bag!
I got washed!
I can't put out to dry!
I feel so fresh and clean!
Sorry, boys.
Maybe try again in a couple hundred years.
Put a call out to all ships and soldiers!
Of course, he's got a plan up his sleeve.
You've always been resourceful, Buddha Sengoku.
So his name is Goldie Ace.
I have any plans left!
I have no clue about it!
Fuck the money!
Old man!
What are you doing up here, not having second thoughts, are you?
No, they chose to be pirates.
They brought this upon themselves.
In that case...
Shut up!
I don't want to talk.
I just want to sit here.
Little idiot!
Whoa, Ace!
What's wrong with you?
You say you want to go out to sea?
Well, now you've got my answer.
Who are you to say I can't?
It's not like you're my father.
I don't have to listen to a thing you tell me, old man.
I'm not old man, I'm Grandpa!
Old man...
Do you want me to show you how much I love you with another punch?
Grandpa!
You know, I'm going to get a lot stronger.
And when I do, I'm going to go out to sea just like it!
Morons!
I don't want either of you becoming pirates!
Hey, don't hit Luffy!
You mean old fart!
What?!
Ace, you come here!
Listen, you never know when a battle might spring up.
So you've got to eat when you can to stay prepared.
And eat a lot.
Every Navy soldier should live by that rule.
So both of you better keep it in mind.
Yeah, well, you don't get to decide that for us, old man.
Yes, I do!
I'm going to be a pirate!
You're going to join the Navy!
Pirate!
Navy!
No!
He ate it all!
I'm stuffed!
I'm going to be the best pirate ever.
Even if Luffy does join the Navy, he won't take orders and he'll eat all the food supplies on whatever ship they put him on.
Probably be less of a nuisance to us if he became a pirate, huh?
I have no sympathy in me for criminals.
But family is a different story.
Now what?
What am I supposed to do?
Ace?
You fool!
Why couldn't you have just listened to me and done what I asked?
Ace.
Trust me on this.
You two really should join the Navy.
Okay?
I know you'll make a strong Navy soldier.
Old man.
If you're feeling any doubt over what must be done, I'm afraid I just can't take pity on you, Garp.
If I had doubts, I would have done something already.
Did you hear what I just heard, Helmepo? What their strategy is?
Yeah.
They're going to bypass the schedule and immediately execute Firefist Ace.
But if they do that...
Huh?
What the...
Hm?
What is that?
Something's falling from the sky!
It's gotta be another surprise ambush from Whitebeard!
you just have to overdo it every time this is because of his death way oh so
it's all my fault cares whose fault it is we're gonna die it's all frozen down
this is not how i picture myself dying somebody help me please i still care about whose fault this
is and it's all yours straw hat damn you
i'm here
Peace!
Luffy and company fall from the sky and land in the middle of the battlefield.
With his brother in sight, Luffy rushes forward as fast as his legs will carry him.
Yet even with his goal in sight, the adversaries before him may prove to be an insurmountable war.
On the next One Piece, Straw Hat Team arrives!
Tension grows at the battlefield!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!